hello everybody and welcome back to my
YouTube channel or welcome to my YouTube
channel I'm call me Chris you could call
me Chris and you are looking extra
scrumptious today darling extra strum
that wasn't I anyway as you can tell
today is going to be a little bit of a
different video on the thumbnail and the
title I'm going to Iceland alone
shocking I'm going to Iceland for a few
reasons first off because I haven't had
any sort of vacation in over 6 and A2
years or so and I also want to go to
Iceland because I've always wanted to go
it looks absolutely stunning with GL and
the northern lights and and everything
and I so I'm I'm super excited to see
the landscape and everything and I'm the
type of person that loves to travel
alone and just kind of do what I want
and I haven't taken more than 3 days off
in a row in the past 6 years or so I'm
constantly preaching on all my channels
to take care of your mental health and
to do self-care and all the important
things and I have neglected to do that
myself and I have not been in the best
mindset lately for the past long while
and I feel like uh it's kind of my
responsibility to be transparent with
you guys because I take such pride in in
preaching about mental health and
everything like that so this trip is for
that it's for me to be able to get away
and free my mind a little bit I really
want this Vlog to be something that's
going to be really organic but also I
wanted to make this video for anybody at
home that's kind of um struggling right
now too because I know that it's not
easy for everybody to travel um I I am
extremely in a very blessed position
right now to be able to to even travel
so this is for anybody at home that
wants a little bit a little bit of
escapism I hope that this video can help
with that a little bit I hope we can see
some beautiful landscape and um we can
kind of go on this little journey
together so yeah but I just want you
guys to know that I I wholeheartedly
appreciate all of your support you've
given me this entire time and um I'm
going to continue to post I'm not like
taking a break or anything like that I'm
just taking this 5 days that's that's
how long I'm going by the way it's 5
days I'm taking this 5 days to just turn
my head off a little bit and I hope this
video helps you turn your head off a
little bit too so let's go to
[Music]
Iceland got through TSA okay I'm a pro
at traveling now I like whip off my
shoes whip out my laptop so now people
are looking at me but what's new and I'm
a basics so I uh I sniffed out the
Starbucks so we're going to get a coffee
even though this is a 11:00 p.m. flight
and I should not be drinking coffee but
I can never sleep on flights anyway I'm
going to get a coffee I acquired my
caramel macchiato and granola bar and
some melatonin gummies which I realize
makes no sense with the coffee but we're
doing it
anyways update I may have taken the
gummies a little too early went not
boarding for another 30 minutes and I'm
like
[Music]
okay fam I have arrived in Ric I am
alone and I have a map I haven't read a
map in a couple of years my phone's
about to die and I can't check into my
hotel until 3:00 it is currently 10 a.m.
so I might get lost in Iceland and I
might live here for the rest of my life
but you know that's all right the lady
at the front desk was like are you alone
and I was just like yeah and she's like
you're traveling alone and I was like
yeah and she's like oh everybody seems
to be sad that I'm alone I'm not though
I'll have a good time I'm going to go
find a little coffee shop cuz your girl
needs coffee and I'm going to read this
map I'm going to lose it so I went into
a gift shop and I bought stuff I
absolutely do not need and absolutely
cannot fit into my bag but I did buy a
toque for the Americans a beanie and
some gloves because I forgot to bring
those things so we got that my phone's
almost going to die so now I need to try
to find a charger so that's the next
mission so update I got lost I asked
somebody on the street who's from here
in Iceland very strong accents by the
way where an electronic stories and he
said look for the two polar bears as big
as me and you'll see a bikini shop and
they'll be Chargers in there so I'm
going to take his word for it we're
going to try to find polar bears and
naked women with bikinis on mannequins
let's try to find that not get hit by a
car oh my god oh dear God I have 10%
battery let's go excited I found the
polar bears there's supposed to be a
bathing suit shop near here I don't
really know which one that is maybe this
one there's no bathing suits in there oh
I found the bathing suits I did it guys
store is closed so now I have to find
Chargers in a different store I'm going
to go in this one see if
[Music]
I at 5% I found a charger at a corner
store right down there but then none of
my cards worked so then I had to go find
an ATM and I got some isk which is the
currency here and I think I got way too
much cuz I didn't know how much hey
anyway my phone's going to die I'm going
to get this charger we're going to be
fine this is where it is I found a
charger I'm so excited and the guy in
the store in that store tested it for me
which was really nice and now I think
I'm going to grab my coffee at this
little place
I found this little spot in the corner
this little window it's really cute
little cafe I ordered a breakfast
sandwich that has like egg salad which
I've never heard of with bacon and other
things I'm exited to try it and a cafe
latte but yeah I'm just going to sit
here and eat my stuff and then try to
find my way back back to the hotel I
guess hopefully I'll be able to check in
by
then look at
this I know this is weird but I've never
gotten a latte like this before and I
feel special I'm going to fit the [__]
out of
[Music]
it look at this it's pretty good to me t
I'm done with my food really living my
main character moment I'll show you some
of the things I got from the store I got
this awesome t-shirt cuz there's a lot
of puffins here they're like known for
their puffins look at this it's like
Godzilla for puffins love that got
little this
thing it's cute matching gloves then as
you see I'm obsessed with bracelets and
rings and stuff I got some they like
lava earrings like from the volcanoes
here I'mma put them on and I got a
bracelet too I don't know where it is in
this bag though let's go out onto the
street again and try to find the
[Music]
Hotel this is like the coolest street
it's the pride street it's so pretty
so
windy I don't know what this is it's
really pretty I'm so
[Music]
lost there's an Irish Pub maybe I'll
stop in it's only noon I'll wait a
couple hours oh a library I'm not going
to read I found this stairwell that
nobody's in and I could do the Joker
dance
[Music]
scum to look I found a dog oh and he
boed it's all right
it's beautiful I'm going to sit down and
enjoy the
[Music]
view I am in the hotel I got so lost
like the last time you guys saw me fast
forward 2 hours I was walking around
thought I had my bearings really didn't
turns out there's like five hotels in
rikic that uh are the Foss hotels so I
went to every single one and the last
one was the right one here I am and you
guys know i' be staying in a bougie
Hotel okay let me give you a little room
tour
okay that's it look how cute this is
there's two I think these are beds for
toddlers like it's literally a single
bed two single beds they're just like
really rubbing in the fact that I'm
single love that also this fridge I can
I love that the saloon very can of them
it's good so tonight I'm staying in
rovic I'm going to wake up in the
morning and I'm taking a bus to
somewhere else I can't pronounce the
name but we'll figure that out tomorrow
if anything happens tonight I'll video
it but until then I'm going take a nap
I'm going to take a shower I stink I
think I walked over 50,000 steps t for
now it is night time and I found this
little restaurant and the menu looks
really good so I'm going to go in and
eat some foods
[Music]
so I had dinner had like the best fish
and chips I've ever eaten in my life
Iceland knows what they're doing and I
know the English people are going to be
in the comments like come to England you
never had English chips before and I
have but it was like 10 years ago so
I'll have to come back to England and
compare but yeah it's so beautiful it's
just like cobblestone streets and I feel
unbelievably safe here it's supposed to
be one of the safest countries in the
world actually but I'm probably going to
head back to the hotel and get some
sleep because I'm going to be up at 7 or
8: a.m. and I'm going to take a bus to
the hot springs and all that kind of
stuff tomorrow so I will see you
[Music]
tomorrow all right fam it is day two we
got the fit check it out we got fleece
boots look at these boots look at these
boots oh These boots are made for
walking and that's just what they'll do
these boots are made for walking the is
the rest of the song Tony just kidding
these walls are so thin that I guarantee
I heard everything last night by the way
there's two couples on either side of me
let me just say these two single beds
made me feel extra single let alone the
noise on either side of these walls all
right anyway today we are going
somewhere to the hot springs Maybe see
Glacier I don't really know where we're
going it's going to be an adventure come
on let's go get some
[Music]
breakfast right now we are at the bridge
between two plates I probably said that
wrong and it's where the North American
tectonic plate meets the euras plate I'm
learning new things every day apparently
they move 2 mm apart every year or
something like that but that's why
there's so much volcanic activity here
it's probably really One D you can't can
hear me but it is beautiful out here
look at it so we're going to go on a
little walk this is the bridge this is
the actual bridge this was the trail to
the bridge let's go
see
whoa these are the two plates that's so
cool almost dropped the camera oh my God
yeah it's nice
here how does the we not be here I don't
know but I'll take it oh you can walk in
it okay I know my shoes are going to get
dirty there if I do it I'm not going to
do
it
[Music]
beautiful this is a better view you can
see the bridge there look the landscape
here is incredible it's amazing I don't
even care that my fingers feel like
they're going to fall off it's they
truly are I might have draw bike but
it's worth it
[Music]
I think the bus is leaving without
me I will show you later today but
[Music]
smells like
eggs
dam look at
that we're at the hot springs
danger look at that Geer my intrusive
thoughts are burning my brain right now
I just want to put my hand in it but I
won't I'm in the Geer smoke right now I
actually oh smells so bad oh look how
pretty that is
you guys can't see it but there's
like that's coming towards
me
oh oh my
god look get through look get Jesus
Christ oh I died
here oh it's so warm okay this is bad I
need it to
stop oh
[Applause]
God oh my God okay oh it smells so
bad getting crop dusted by a giant fart
this is what I was just stuck in this
plume of sulver smoke so
[Music]
cool look everybody getting stuck in it
it's like walking into an avalanche
let's go back through I'm going to run
through this time I'm running me oh
that's actually really cool actually
that's a good idea walk into the abyss
oh no
no okay okay that
was so oh God I want to give you guys my
POV right now cuz I can't see anything
it's like a video game 5 minutes
remaining oh there we
go yeah be careful watch your
step they're going to die
[Music]
look at this how pretty look at that
that's where I want to live right there
on the little island all alone but it's
so pretty and then there's a a
lighthouse right there which I would
also live alone it's just really lonely
um but it's beautiful the statue freaked
me out cuz I thought this was a real
bird but it's just a statue but let's go
over here this is our uh last stop in
like the lava fields that I think we're
going to go see some other stuff I don't
know I don't know what's going on I'm
just on the bus living my best life oh
wow that's pretty
[Music]
I'm sorry what is oh my God from euro
vision that's so funny home of the
volcano man at this exact spot stood
will frell and Rachel McAdams and
performed volcano man from the Hollywood
movie your a vision contest you know
I'mma stand right there you know I'mma
do it
[Music]
like it's like it's fake this is
incredible not going to lie though it
smells so much like sulfur it smells
like just a giant giant wet fart here
but you know what the landscape it's
beautiful enough to to mask the smell
you know what I mean it's just in these
fields though as you can see there's
like Geo fuel I don't know they like get
the steam from the ground you know what
she explained it really well I can't
explain it look at up this
bird his name is Tony and I love him I
got to get back in the van God I'm
always the last one
[Music]
did I almost fall down this crass
maybe very good the Blue Lagoon which is
like one of our famous pools in
Iceland so excited ready to go in the
Blue Lagoon
[Music]
it's so cold SK warm oh it's so
warm oh my God it's so nice it's so
nice oh my gosh it's so warm it's like
the perfect
temperature oh my God I could live in
here I never want to leave this is so
far this is the best part this is the
best part of Iceland so far not going to
lie there's facts if you guys want to
read them it's funny there's like
certain points in the pool where it's
like actually kind of cold and then it's
like really hot like my M relationship
I'm in Bliss is this what it feels like
to be not mentally ill cuz I love
it float with
me I'm so boring
[Music]
guys I found a little cave that nobody's
in oh this is coold I feel like there
would be like a really big fish that
would come and eat
me why did I put that in my head there's
no fish in here I don't think they could
survived but this is cute
[Music]
well I'm having a very relaxing time I'm
going to actually now enjoy this I'll
put my phone down and I'll see you guys
at lunch
[Music]
we are done with the Blue Lagoon we got
in the car and we are now heading to the
active lava Fields I'm excited look how
gorgeous we're going to go on like 45
minute hike or something oh here's a
sign volcano Skelly exit I just tripped
on a rock let's
[Music]
go see all the steam coming up you just
fall in in right there burn your foot
off I just think of Star Wars this is so
cool though is a steep hill another
[Music]
shirt the volcano the hard far away
let's go not jump on the lava look how
pretty
wow see all the lava coming down to here
so cool do not walk do not throw do not
make
carvings do not give into impulsive
thoughts
basically looks like job of the
Hut this is
lava oh almost on
it wow that's so cool look at
that almost
[Music]
fell you have no idea how bad I want to
I want to jump on this [__] I can touch
it though I asked her she said it's okay
look it we'll touch it
together oh I don't know if you can see
me oh yeah can Feels Like a Rock feel
like that's not that oh this is cool
though look at
this
ooh ah I still can't get over this just
looks like what's that Rocky guy from
the oh Fantastic 4 that's what it looks
like coming back
[Music]
hotel look at
the and stuff out there so pretty and
we're going to have an Icelandic dinner
so I'll see you there
lamb pasta R gross that is delicious the
lamb is so good dinner was Fab I didn't
want to film there I was sitting with
like 12 other people and I just didn't
have it in me to film me eating you know
so it was good it was lamb and some
pastry thing and some pasta it was
interesting but it was good I want to go
to bed I'm setting an alarm for like
1:00 a.m. though to see if I can go see
the Northern Lights so we'll see if I
wake up for that but until then we'll
see you
Manana day three we headed off to go
make and eat some geothermal bread which
is essentially bread that is baked in
the ground and uses a heat from the hot
springs okay we've been dipping our
hands in random puddles and this is a
warm puddle ow it's actually gotot
actually really
hot we're all 5 years old and like
apparently this is warm
too oh it is
oh I would swim in that they're digging
out the bread all right let's go there
with the shovel okay hello everyone what
we're going to see today we're going to
see today how I plan a big bread but
you'll just see in a
[Music]
moment oh my god oh oh yeah
wow baptizing
[Music]
bread we cover it in two layers of
plastic time for the big
reveal
toat so yeah what's left to do now I
guess to eat it so I invite you back
inside and we're going to taste it with
some other Icelandic goodies ooh maybe
some rotten shark I don't know shark
after she revealed the sweet dirt bread
we ate it with some butter and some fish
and it was so good and then we headed
off to see more
geysers our next stop is the Geyers
we're going to go look at some steam
coming out of the ground it's kind of
terrifying there's people up there oh
look at that oh god oh it's going to
come right at me oh God we're going to
run
oh
no got of my eye
whoa holy
[__] okay that was cool it's windy so I
don't know if you can hear me but I'm
probably going to head back to the bus
saw a couple guys I'll see you guys at
the next
stop we are at the last stop of the day
which is
waterfall some mountains over there
let's go see
waterfalls W it's funny you can feel the
water hitting your face from the
waterfalls look at
[Music]
this incredible it's crazy
gorgeous God can you imagine tubing down
that thing God damn that'd be a way to
go but uh I I'm not for me not no
[Music]
I can just jump in there right now I
won't looks nice though I was just
taking some pictures or like some
selfies of myself and this really nice
guy was taking photos of me while I
wasn't looking and then he came up up to
me and air dropped the photos to me so I
thought that was really nice cuz I'm
alone so it's hard to take pictures so
thank you to that random Australian
stranger you are very sweet amazing I
love people everybody I've met here has
been so kind all the Icelandic people
Australian people Irish people I met so
many different people it's just amazing
[Music]
short tastes good after that that tastes
good oh oh it smells really bad do you
chew it and I just swallow
it oh nope nope I'm not I can't I can't
I can't I can't the texture it's in my
mouth that is alcohol
I put the fish in my mouth we just ate
green one shark I just found out and
it's poisonous our tour gues trying to
poison us it wasn't that
bad what is this fish soup it's
good I am out here it is midnight and
we're looking at the Northern Lights
probably cannot see them on the camera I
will insert photos
[Music]
like her
tornado oh my God I'm so glad I came
back out like I'm going to call it a
this just thousand times better look at
it almost there too sh were you calling
me day four we got up nice and early and
ate some Brey and then we went off to
see some waterfalls which I loved and
boy am I glad I brought waterproof and
windproof gear this day we got wet and
just pounded by the wind
[Music]
[Applause]
too cool
[Music]
[Applause]
SOC Co
[Music]
nobody else is down here for good reason
it's so wet look how
cool you always got to go the path Less
Traveled you know W so cool
[Music]
epic oh it's so cold I'm going back I'm
going to go get a hot chocolate this is
wor it though here at the next one it's
in a
[Music]
gge going to like balance on the rocks
we made
it I got soaked in there holy [__] can't
feel my hands work though all insert
some photos
here he like coming
so
windy it's like blowing the bus off the
[Music]
road there's a bus that went off the
road so hopefully ours doesn't do that
we're parked and the bus is shaking I
don't know that was a question I maybe
the
restaurant the wind was getting a little
too strong so we stopped for some lunch
at this cute little
[Laughter]
restaurant this people oh no it's so
windy I'm going to try to go out there
right now I'm terrified but let's try it
oh my
God try to
go
sh not even
fa
oh oh my God
it's a t with
me it's so
windy that these let's calm down right
now for a sec oh it's I got behind this
thing so it's not as windy here these
feel like shards of glass hitting your
face holy
[__] was it worth it probably not I just
couldn't guess it
[Applause]
[Music]
o
[Applause]
never felt so
buly never felt I can't speak I've never
felt bullied by Mother
Nature
okay I try to fight her fight Mother
Nature you never
[Music]
so update we are currently
stuck uh the roads are closed because on
one of the buses toed over the one that
I showed before it had fully tipped over
so they're fixing that and also there
was an earthquake um and there's a fent
volcano that has not exploded in 50
years that just had an earthquake so
they're on watch for that so we're just
going to go on a little hike to pass the
time for now so yeah let's go do that
found the
waterfall gorgeous beautiful look at
this Canyon little less wind here which
is nice ah so awesome looks fake I'm
ruining it by being a
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think this is the fourth waterfall of
today it's really
pretty there's a dog
there we got missed
yeah woo
[Music]
not a bad View
he
I don't think I was supposed to come
down here but I did now I got to go back
over there let's
[Music]
go my tour guy got mad at me she's right
there in the yellow
got some ice
cream
good so I enjoyed my ice cream and
reminisced about all the beautiful
waterfalls I saw that day and then we
headed back to the hotel and had some
lovely dinner and then day five
[Music]
by so it used to be all the way over
there and now it's melted all the way to
there
[Music]
this was absolutely amazing to see in
person so amazing that I forgot to film
a lot of it I'm really sorry but I hope
you enjoy the footage I did
[Music]
get going back down
thank you
[Music]
all in all Iceland was an amazing trip
it was absolutely incredible it was
exactly what I needed to be honest and
Iceland is AB absolutely stunning and
the people were so nice not to mention
their Stellar Cuisine I ate a lot of
fish and I enjoyed every bite of
it and the people I met along the way
made the trip even
better I hope to come back someday for
sure but I hope you enjoyed this video
and were able to escape a little with me
I appreciate you guys so much and thank
you for watching I'll see your beautiful
face in the next video thanks